翻译：@隐秀_（seriouszyx）
The big aha is to realize that if every node simply had a pointer to whoever was behind it,
重点要意识到，如果每个节点都简单地有一个指向其背后的人的指针
we never need to scan forward from the front
我们就永远不需要从正面向前扫描
to find our predecessor.
去找我们前面的人
So in other words, if fifty had a pointer back to the node containing nine
换句话说，如果50有一个指向包含9的节点的指针
and the node with nine in it had a pointer back at three
包含9的节点的指针指回3
and this node has a pointer back at the sentinel.
这个节点指回哨兵节点
Then if we wanted to find any of our previous is we just follow that pointer.,
如果我们想找到以前的任何东西，只需遵循这个指针
so we end up with this step apology here,
我们在这里总结
where each node has not just an item and the next pointer but also a previous pointer
每个节点不仅有一项和 next 指针，还有 previous 指针
and in that way um this list structure is often called a doubly linked list
这样，这个 List 结构通常被称为“双向链表”
each node has two links
每个节点有两个链接
and that's as opposed to what we had before which was a singly linked our only forward pointing list
而这与我们之前的情况不同，以前是一个单链的、只向前指的 List
and so singly linked list by the way is what SLList  stood for
顺便说一下，单链表是 SLList 的代表
now you know
现在你知道了
so this approach is wonderful
这个方法很棒
And that once we've added these two links
一旦我们添加了这两个链接
our add methods faster get methods fast and are removed method from either of the ends as fast
我们添加和获取方法更快，而且删除方法一样快
so any operations involving the end of the list will take constant time
任何涉及 List 末尾的操作都只需要恒定的时间
though operations in the middle will be slower
但是中间的操作速度会更慢
and we'll talk about alternative approaches for dealing with those later
我们稍后会讨论处理这些问题的替代方法
but as far as linked lists go this is the way that linked lists are typically done
但就链表而言，这是链式链表的典型做法
Now this approach
这种方法
while it works
当它工作时
it has this one limitation
它有一个限制
which You will only really feel and come to understand if you're trying to code this thing up
只有你试图用它编码，你才会真正感受并开始理解这一点
there is a special case
有一个特例
which is that the last pointer sometimes points at the sentinel
那就是 last 指针有时指向哨兵
and it sometimes points out what we'll call a real node
有时会指向所谓的真实节点
and so while that might not seem such a big deal
虽然这看起来并不是什么大不了的事
here once you try and code it up
一旦你尝试用它编码
you'll see that for each of your methods you'll start running into these annoying
你在每个方法中都将开始遇到这些恼人的问题
if statements you have to check and see if it's actually the sentinel
你必须检查它是否真的是哨兵
so we want to avoid that
我们想要避免这种情况
so what we can do
我们能做的是
is try and be a little more pure
试着让它更纯粹一点
we're going to look to the heavens for inspiration and try and think how can I make this just more perfect.
我们仰望苍天寻找灵感，努力思考如何才能让这一切更加完美
So the most natural way to perfect our approach
完善我们的方法最自然的方式
is to add a second sentinel
就是增加第二个 sentinel
we could say--- instead of having a last pointer that points to the last item
last 指针不再指向最后一项
we're going to have a sentinel on both ends
我们的两端都会有一个哨兵
because now we have front and back pointers or sorry next and previous pointers
因为现在我们有 next 指针和 previous 指针
we can have a sensible that's always at the front and one that's always at the back
我们前后都要始终有一个理智的人
so that the empty list has a pointer--- has a sentinel here at the front and a sentinel here at the back
所以空链表在前面有一个哨兵，在后面有一个哨兵
and then as we add items to our list
当我们向 List 中添加项目时
we end up just ssliding them in between the two sentinels.
把它们塞到两个哨兵中间就行了
so this approach is nicer
这种方法更好
it'll be much easier to code up than the naive approach
它比幼稚的方法更容易编码
and it'll be equally powerful
也同样强大
and this is one approach you can use for project one
这是你可以用于项目一的方法
Now while this approach is nice and easy to code up
虽然这种方法很好并且很容易编码
I think there's one better approach
但我认为有一个更好的方法
this is the approach that if you went up to the mountain where the monk is like hanging out in the mountaintop temple
如果你登上山峰，碰到在寺庙闲逛的和尚
and you said what is truly the best doubly linked list
你问什么才是最好的双向链表
and you had to use a long climb
你必须花很长时间攀登
and you had to it was just excruciating to get up there and you really are asking for answers
你不得不这么做，攀登很痛苦，但你求知若渴
this is what you would get
你将得到此法
in this approach
在此方法中
instead of having a sentinel on either end, you're going to have one sentinel
用一个哨兵代替两端的哨兵
that is both the front  and the back
既是最先也是最后
well how can that be?
那怎么可能呢？
you might ask your---
你可以问问...
You know the monk atop the hill
山顶上的和尚
and he might say well
他可能会说
whenever you have an empty list
你有一个空链表时
the previous is the sentinel itself
previous 是哨兵本身
and the next is the sentinel itself
next 也是哨兵本身
and at that point you're getting irritated at the monk and you just want answers
你为此对和尚很恼火，你只是想要答案
and you have to reflect a little that's part of the glory of some of the most beautiful ideas
你必须反思一下，这是最美好想法的闪耀之处
they take a lot of deep thought to really get
它们经过深思熟虑才能真正领悟
but in this case as you add items to the to the central list
在本例中，当你向 List 中间添加项时
you'll find that there's a very natural place to add them
会发现可以很自然地添加
so after we add the numbers three and nine
比如添加完3和9后
for example, we would say the sentinel, it's next is three
sentinel 的 next 是3
because that's the first thing they added
因为这是第一个添加的
and then it's next to nine
它的 next 是9
and then its next is the sentinel again
然后它的 next 又是 sentinel
so in effect it's kind of like the fact you know the world's round
就像地球是圆的
if I keep going in one direction around the world that come back to where I start
如果我一直朝一个方向走，就会回到开始的地方
and that's this approach
这就是这种方法
and so for example if I do sentinel
举个例子，假设我是“哨兵”
dot next dot next dot next
next、next 再 next
I'm back to where I started so this arrow in purple is sentinel dot next dot next dot next
我回到了开始的地方，所以这个紫色的箭头是哨兵的 next 的 next 的 next
which is just the sentinel
还是一个哨兵
And so all this idea may seem more confusing and a little silly.
所有这些想法可能看起来更加混乱、有点愚蠢
I encourage you when you do project one do this
我鼓励你在项目一时这样做
understand the wisdom of the monk atop the hill
理解山顶和尚的智慧
and enlightenment will be yours
你就开悟了
so that's it as far as are doubly linked lists go in terms of logical improvements
这就是双向链表在逻辑上的改进
and so just to summarize what we did there
简单总结一下
improvement seven was adding a dot last pointer  to the last item on the list
改进七是添加了指向 List 中最后一项的 last 指针
and dot previous says everything should look behind it
.previous 表明一切都应该往后看
but the problem there is that
但问题是
for each of our methods one dap with special cases
每种方法都要面临一个特殊情况
owing to the fact that to this situation here
由于这样的事实
this special case we described before
这是之前描述过的特殊情况
so to avoid those special cases in each of our methods
为了避免每个方法中的特殊情况
we can either have two sentinels
我们设置了两个哨兵
or we can make our list circular and this is the approach I recommend for project one because it's cool
或者我们可以使 List 循环，这是我为项目一推荐的方法，因为它很酷
so to summarize all the things we've done
所以总结一下
in the previous lecture we made the SLList improvements one through six
在上一讲中，我们对 SLList 进行了一至六的改进
in this lecture we've made this list seven and eight
本节课我们进行了七和八的改进
and so there's many more things before we would be up to par with the built-in linked list that's in Java
与 Java 内置链表的水平相比，我们仍有很大差距
for example adding exceptions
比如添加异常
and various other features
以及各种其他功能
and we'll discuss those over the coming weeks
我们将在接下来的几周讨论这些问题
but that's the core of what makes a doubly linked list
但这就是双重链表的核心所在
so there's a little bit more we're going to say now about making our linked list even better
现在我再多说一点，让我们的链表变得更好
翻译：@隐秀_（seriouszyx）